It can take a lifetime to feel alive.
The Mother is a drama, romance film directed by Roger Michell.
A grandmother has a passionate affair with a man half her
age, who is also sleeping with her daughter.
May, played by Anne Reid.
Darren, played by Daniel Craig.
Toots, played by Peter Vaughan.
Bobby, played by Steven Mackintosh.
Paula, played by Cathryn Bradshaw.
Helen, played by Anna Wilson-Jones.
The Mother is a 2003 British drama film directed by Roger
Michell and written by Hanif Kureishi.
It stars Anne Reid, Daniel Craig, Peter Vaughan,
Steven Mackintosh, and Cathryn Bradshaw.
The film had its world premiere at the 2003 Cannes Film
Festival in the Directors Fortnight section.
The film explores themes of parent child relationship, love
affair, older woman younger man relationship.
The tone is emotional.